hey my name's garland nixon and i'm live
unfortunately due to the uh storm uh my
my dear friend and uh partner in crime
john kiriakou uh doesn't have any
electricity he's sitting in the dark so
john's not going to be able to do
anything with us
with us today but uh he'll be back soon
uh hopefully hopefully within the next
week sometime at least john will get
electricity but we need to talk
because the afghanistan war is over but
that means nothing to the neo neo-cons
they are still up to their miscreant
behavior and they're looking for more
wars and more trouble let's talk
now that look that timing didn't go over
so well did it let's try it again let's
try it again
let's talk
[Music]
hello hello garland nixon here and it's
a weird night um storms all over the
place and unfortunately for all of us my
dear friend john kiriakou who was
supposed to be on tonight is sitting in
the dark and has been for a while he
says it's quite relaxing but
unfortunately a little too relaxing
because john will not be able to join us
tonight uh hopefully he'll have
electricity back sometime within the
next week
and uh uh we'll be able to get them back
on i'm sure uh maybe tomorrow or friday
we shall see all right so we're going to
talk about afghanistan
but not afghanistan anymore
let's talk about what's next after after
afghanistan here is one of the results
here oh crap i can't tell here we go
that's closing uh
okay here we go that'll do it that'll do
it all right so let's look at this
interesting article
here's an article
where we see the neocons already
starting their move
they are not happy with joe biden why
are they not happy with joe biden
because he got out of afghanistan right
and
okay good great that's fine we should
have got out of afghanistan but
i ain't given joe biden the uh nobel
peace prize quite yet okay so what's the
neocons first move look at this madison
cawthon prompts kamla harris to conjure
up the 25th change and take power a
republican politician resident
uh participant composed the letter
thursday to vice head of state kamala
harris asking that she'd take power
under the 25th amendment madison
hawthorne north carolina republican
prompted ms harris to start the
procedure of getting rid of head of
state biden from workplace as no longer
capable of discharging his duties all
right interesting so that's number one
it and that is they're so mad with biden
and we're gonna talk about this they're
so angry with joe biden
they're ready to get get him out of here
and get kamilah harrison well i can
think of one reason if you're a
republican i can think of one reason
right off the bat where you might want
kamala harris in
because she ain't going to be hard to
beat oh god you know i'll just speak
short briefly on kamala harris and she's
her name is there
um she's just just another abysmal
mistake by the democratic party and it's
not a mistake you know to say the
democrats
um are making a mistake
by
putting camel harrison there would be
like if you go bass fishing and you
throw a particular lure out and the bite
and and and the bass bites it
is it an error for the
bass to bite that particular lure yes it
is but he bites it because he's a bass
and that's what he does and he's like
hey that looks like a minnow i think
i'll bite it well it ain't a minnow and
he gets caught well
bass don't taste so good so hopefully
you've released the bass but whatever
the case
the nature of a bass
is to bite
a rubber minnow or whatever it is a
rubber worm whatever he goes after the
nature of the bass is to bite that so he
didn't make a mistake he just did what
he does so the democratic party didn't
make a mistake
we could argue it was a terrible error
to choose
to choose a candidate who in the
primaries
didn't get a single delegate she had to
drop out before iowa she was a pathetic
a pathetic candidate for president and
wouldn't you know they chose her you
know that's like you know um it's nfl
season right and the teams just had to
cut down to their final roster and
decide who their starting quarterback
was it would be like picking the person
that couldn't even make his high school
team and then when you get ready to
start you'll you'll go like hey what
about that guy well he he always throws
it to the wrong team and he doesn't know
how to read defenses and he's just slow
a foot
and and he's he's you know he couldn't
even make the team his jv team in high
school oh okay we'll choose him guess
what you ain't winning many games that's
what they did
there's a reason that kamala harris
didn't
didn't do very well
to be kind didn't do well in the
primaries because she's a very bad
politician she's not a good politician
she doesn't have the things that it
takes to be a good politician she
doesn't have the tools it takes i'm not
i'm not talking about her intellect
their emotional tools their cur tools of
charisma
their tools of how you communicate to
people how you make people like you
things like that she don't have any of
those she's really bad and they've
chosen her now the only asset that she
has is that she's a very good puppet is
that she's a climber so she'll do
whatever she's told to do and they could
stick her up there and then they could
use this protection she's a woman of
color why you can't uh put her down you
can't denigrate her as a politician
she's a woman of color and there are
people that'll buy into that crap but i
won't she's a bad politician she's a bad
politician she's horrible so the first
thing they think is
they're like and hey let's uh get biden
out get camera and camera in we can tell
her she's a climber any damn thing we
tell her to do she's gonna do the empire
pushed back against biden the empire was
like no we're an empire and what an
empire does is one thing an empire only
sees two types of nations nations that
we have conquered and nations that we
intend to conquer and that's what the
war mongers and imperialists believe and
joe biden leading the empire here's a
country that we've conquered the empire
will never give up a country that it
conquered joe biden did it so he might
as well be trump they that now the
warmongers hate him so bad in fact
they'd prefer trump over him because
trump you know uh
doubled down on most of the stuff
they're probably crying in their soup oh
god
we didn't kept trump he was we could run
anything by him and we could bamboozle
me do it well so
that's part of it uh and and so
the they're looking right now what
what's going on i think here's the other
part of it so they're thinking oh what
can we do what was me there's weeping
and gnashing of teeth in neoconville
because joe biden's president and he's
taken the neocons toy which was
afghanistan out from under him but do
not fret
yes do not cry dear neocons you haven't
lost yet you see joe biden still is a um
is a warmonger joe biden's history is
clear of neoconism maybe not quite as
much as all of them but far too much for
most of us
so the truth is while most of us are
thinking hmm
you got people about to get thrown out
on the street you got our infrastructure
falling apart you got things going bad
at here i guess the president you know
here in america i guess the president
look out for us uh joe biden and crew
are thinking about that they're thinking
about the empire you ain't you you're
they're not into you okay you're not
part of the equation you can die on the
street starve and freeze to death with
no health care they don't give a damn
that is not what the empire does so
let's continue on
so and that's uh let's see coop w says
oh there we go you beat an empire you
will pay forever for making them look
bad yeah that's that's that they're
going to try but the problem is they
have is and forgive me if i take my
glasses off because they're kind of
screwed up here and i got to fix them
but the part of it is
they want to
make afghanistan pay forever but the
truth of the matter is the empire is
weakening and the us empire doesn't have
the power it used to have so it can't
wield power around the world willy-nilly
because you've got other countries
russia china iran these countries are
growing and they're getting more
powerful and that's why the u.s has them
in its sights the us is looking at them
saying darn these people they're strong
enough that they don't have to listen to
us anymore we got to take them all down
every last one of them right
it's madness so what's happening we got
a couple things we've got
the oh you know what let me find here uh
i got another another art another good
article let's see
we've got
and this is this is certainly um
certainly of consequence so i'll share
that with you and we'll talk about this
and this is part of the conversation
all right
we've got house set up to tear but how
set to terror biden's pentagon budget
plans republicans and even some
democrats are planning to
boost funding levels
well we'll fix you joe biden darn your
hyde
you're going to pull out of afghanistan
to save money we'll give you even more
money for the pentagon
that's it we'll fix you and they're not
putting more money in the pentagon
budget because they ain't planning to
use it they're putting it in there
because they're planning to use it
so the neocons are looking for more
they're looking for war they're mad
they're furious at joe biden
because he uh
failed to hold on to a land that they
had conquered
and now
they're looking to move forward a couple
of uh uh one of the things that the
neocons are looking at is ethiopia
there's if you go into the news you'll
find a lot of articles where they're
looking at ethiopia and if you look at
the washington post you'll start the
propaganda seeing the propaganda now you
know
how it works the us wants to go invade
overthrow occupy another country get
involved in some kind of a military
practice there's a number of things you
got to do we
you know the game first of all the
leader of that country whoever it may be
is a
fill in the blank uh
is a dictator
is an authoritarian
is a autocrat and don't forget we've got
to go there for humanitarian reasons to
make life better and
women gay people we got to look up for
them you know all the lies they put
they're the same ones so the washington
post has already started they had an
article saying oh the people the troops
and uh
in ethiopia they're raping women and
they're doing this and that and they're
starting to build the case because the
the um the neocons and warmongers in dc
are hungry they lost a war that's a
country they lost the country and they
dog gone at all they need another one
and they're sick and tired of this
business about giving up countries that
we've already conquered so they're
looking for another one i wouldn't
advise ethiopia i wouldn't advise that
area there are a lot of fighters there
who um
have
a lot of experience who are battle
hardened who've been fighting for a long
time you get in there you know you saw a
black hawk down you know somalia
ethiopia you're gonna go there you're
gonna have problems you're gonna lose a
lot of people but you know here's the
bottom line the neocons don't care if
you lose a lot of people because the
people ain't going to be them they're
hungry and they got to eat they're going
to get paid now they now there's another
uh thing you might there's a
a a couple other stories if i can look
i'll do it in real time here
um
another place of horrifyingly or
horrifyingly that you might want to look
at
is
ukraine
and uh one of the things that happened
today joe biden met with um with the
with the vladimir vladimir
zielinski he's the president of ukraine
and that's a place where you can dump a
lot of money it's right on russia's
border they can they can pretend um that
they're helping ukraine they can pretend
they're looking out for the ukrainians
against the evil russians and they can
sink a lot of money look they've already
gotten paid real heavy biden got paid
real heavy his boy went there and you
know worked uh worked the uh the gas
angle and he he got paid heavy so they
already know they can go to air and they
can launder a lot of money there's a lot
of corruption in the same way there was
a lot of corruption in um
afghanistan notice a pattern you go to a
country there's a lot of corruption and
nobody's gonna notice that some of that
corruption money flows right back into
your pocket um here's the problem with
ukraine
the problem is it's on the russian
border and the russian military is
powerful very very very
people consider it the second most
powerful military in the world behind
the us but there's a caveat to that
and that is this
while people consider the russian
military the second most powerful
military in the world
it ain't spread out you see the russian
military is set up as a defensive
military it's set up to operate within
two three four five hundred kilometers
max you know two three four hundred
miles of russia it's set up to protect
russia and the perimeter rights out
outside of russia now imagine if we the
us military if we didn't have troops all
over the world 750 bases and we didn't
have our you know uh uh a ship cells
encircling china imagine if we had all
of that equipment and all of those
people back here how powerful our
military would be nobody would be able
it's powerful as it is but nobody would
be able to penetrate it well that's what
russia's done they got their people home
on their border which means they've got
a really powerful defensive military i
mean many people say you know well first
of all
if they wanted to take europe they
probably could us and nato couldn't stop
them
they'd roll right over them like a speed
bump it's a powerful powerful military
so the reality is um
the idea
that you're going to go into ukraine and
get a war with russia is suicide for the
ukrainians and if you military any
military that goes in there the u.s nato
troops go in there they'll get rolled
over like a st speed bump all of them
this is a world class superpower
military and ukraine's sitting on the
border of that world-class super uh uh
uh uh world-class class uh military and
in it there's it's just too close
there's nothing you can do to protect
ukraine so that's why i've got an
article up right here biden pledges 60
million in military ukraine they're
going to give them whatever it's a waste
of time it's not a waste excuse me it's
money laundering they're going to give
more money to um this is going to shock
you raytheon to buy javelin missiles um
which are anti-tank missiles and sending
sending them to ukraine well that ain't
going to do no good you know why because
there ain't no tank battle
what good are they going to do number
one number two the russians would crush
them if there really was a military the
russian military would crush the
ukrainian military so quickly there
wouldn't be time for a tank battle it
would be
a uh it would be like an elephant
stepping on an ant so when the us gives
money to ukraine military aid to ukraine
to protect themselves from russia it's a
fraud they couldn't protect themselves
from that russia it's too powerful it
would be like giving money to canada to
protect or mexico to protect themselves
from the us military if the us military
was all right here within our borders it
would be a waste of time
but it's money laundering
so the us
for those of you who think well maybe
ukraine's the idea
uh i'm gonna say that it ain't
because it would be suicide immediately
i mean they wouldn't you know they had
some coup w put six minute war exactly
exactly it would be white flag time for
the ukraine it would it would be over
for ukraine so
that's uh not an option i think the only
thing that i can see right now
uh for the for the neocons is to go is
to start moving into africa and that's
going to be deadly there's a lot of
battle-hardened troops there's a lot of
places so they can go in there they can
kill a lot of people i also wonder also
because there's a lot of black folks in
africa there's a lot of black folks in
the us and the us military if some of
the people in the us military and some
of the black people in america may start
to lose
really they may really bleed support for
military if it's if it's africa it'd be
interesting to see if that happens not
interesting excuse me that's the wrong
word it's almost like i'm looking at it
clinically we're talking about murdering
people but the bottom line is that's
where our us military currently is um is
looking and the um
and let me put another way and this is
what i think is really twisted if you
read what's coming out of
england the neocons in england basically
they're almost coming across like this
hey you took our war
and uh
you know we don't have any war we had a
war now we don't have a war anymore you
owe us a war where's our war joe biden
oh you took one from us you owe us a new
one
um now yak says you could go to south
america too that's a possibility yak yak
you you could go to south america too
that's another thought thanks for the
and for those out there who are who are
uh involved you know put your uh put
your your thoughts here and i'll and
i'll share them and we can talk south
america there's a couple things going on
in south america so what are the options
option one is venezuela venezuela ain't
a pretty option talk from a person who's
been to venezuela traveled around
venezuela talked to people in venezuela
then in venezuela about 30 million
people um the reason the u.s wants to
overthrow venezuela is to steal their
oil
i mean let's be honest about it they got
more oil than any country in the world
and the u.s has already stolen the
country of city the company of citgo
wants to steal their oil but
let me tell you what i know about
venezuela from studying it and from
spending time in venezuela and traveling
around the country and talking to people
in venezuela going to the mountains
talking to the poor people in the small
villages and towns here's what i can
tell you
so the us uh
you know had uh for a long long period
of time had venezuela as a client state
um
er eventually hugo chavez um overtook
you know was able to to take over the
country and he did a lot for poor people
and the poor people had nothing and he
did a lot for poor people built free
houses gave them food and they were
impoverished with nothing did a lot of
things i said you know they they a lot
of them lived in the mountains he built
this gigantic cable car system they're
like red where they could get on these
cable cars for free come in town to
caracas into the city and uh shop get
jobs whatever and they could ride in
that and they didn't have they didn't
pay anything so he did a lot for the
poor people so they loved it right
because before they were impoverished
they you know mistreated by the us they
got nothing this is the reality what
whatever you think of it this is the
reality that was a country where a lot
of people were poor while it was under
the jurisdiction of the us
and under chavez he did a lot maduro was
chavez ii in charge and um the truth of
the matter is go to their they love it
they like him this crap about he's a
dictator and they and they don't like
maduro well that's for people who've
never been there
hugo chavez is a saint to the poor
people which is the majority he is
literally i mean to them he is a saint
to the poor people of venezuela and
maduro was his second in charge so he
can do no wrong to be honest
okay that's a reality i'm not making a
judgment on a good writer and different
but i'm telling you there your people
that are saying he's some kind of
dictator and the people don't want him
are giving you a line of crap that ain't
the truth and i remember going out to
small villages and small towns in the
mountains and women
women standing there shaking their fists
saying to me
we will protect our democracy we are the
chavistas we are the sons and daughters
of chavez right
that's a fact so regardless of the
propaganda if the u.s decides now let me
add this think about this
you might have heard look it up
something called the bay of piglets and
that was when uh under the trump
administration some idiots decided they
were going to overthrow um
venezuela since we're talking about a
possibility of of venezuela as being the
next target or
of the neocons
so they had about 60 of these
mercenaries and their plan was
and a hapless plan it was i might add
their plan was to um come into to get on
boats to come into venezuela by um sea
and to make their way to
um
to maduro's home wherever it was to
kidnap him take him and overthrow the
country that was their brilliant plan
right well it ran awry really early i've
been there and what i've found is
a significant number of people you'll
see the military everywhere they've got
the dark green military fatigues but
then you see other people who have light
brown similar those are the that's the
militia a lot a lot of people are belong
to it millions of people belong to the
militia and those who don't belong
aspire to belong to the militia and that
is basically like our reserves
and they're ready to fight and many of
them are armed and that's to protect
their country nothing wrong i accept
that okay
so the bay of piglets a bunch of
mercenaries who are out of uh paid out
of florida decide to land well there are
a bunch of fishermen see them coming in
the fishermen are armed
they the fishermen fire on them kill
some of them and capture the rest now
think about this they're coming in and
they get captured by fishermen literal
fishermen beat them
take them out in a firefight and take
them all because there was too many
fishermen why because
that's what you're facing in venezuela
the people are very well armed and they
and as they say
we will protect our democrat i'll never
forget well little women in this we will
protect our democracy we will fight for
our democracy they literally are ready
to fight in their arms so if the us
decides they're going to go into
venezuela it's going to be like like
iraq those people will fight them
they'll shoot they will they all hell's
going to break loose we don't want to go
there there will be extremely heavy
losses and a lot of them so venezuela is
probably not a good option for the
neocons to choose next will they bomb
and kill people yeah but sooner or later
you got to put soldiers on the ground
my brother-in-law's retired special
forces all that kind of stuff and he
says sooner or later it's a man with a
rifle sooner or later you got to put
somebody
on the ground with a rifle and when you
do and see what these countries know is
you can fly over and bomb and all this
we'll just dig in you do that and sooner
or later when you come in with men with
rifles that's when we're going to go to
town and that's what would happen with
venezuela what could we bomb what could
we bomb in all likelihood the people in
the military would probably blend off
into the into with the rest of the poor
folks and then when our soldiers came in
they'd light them up it would be like a
rock it would be a a slog but probably
worse because man in iraq the people
hated saddam hussein so they wouldn't
fight for saddam hussein they fought
because we were invaders in venezuela
the poor people there loved maduro and
they loved as they said we're the sons
and daughters of chavez they would fight
to the death every last one of them it
would be hell for america it would be
hell on earth for american soldiers to
go to venezuela let me tell you from a
person who has been there and spent time
and talked to the people we don't want
to do that
oh sam clayhand yeah he already knows he
says i drive a toyota in flip-flops if
you say you're right if you want to beat
the us empire from the looks of things
from the looks of things all you need to
do
is uh get yourself a toyota truck and
put about 12 guys in the back of it and
some flip-flops and you're going to
probably you're probably going to defeat
m1 abrams tanks and everything else
that's the way it works
so at any rate so and then when you go
around south america the problem is it's
close to home it's hard to hide and it's
very it's going to be very difficult for
the u.s to use military force
in south america and so what the us has
traditionally done traditionally
particularly in recent years is gone
more with
the cia training death squads and
horrific unthinkable things like that
but
um
you know the the the long and short of
it is i don't think south america is is
a very strong option for the neocons for
the next war i think they're probably
looking at south america and the
question is does joe biden want to dig
himself into another war you know let's
not forget they're also thinking iran oh
they'd love to go to war with iran that
would be a bad move again that would be
a devastating move iran's a very
powerful country extremely powerful
military country and what iran has for
you for those of you don't know number
one they've got a lot of allies in the
area right they got a lot of
they got hamas they got hezbollah
they've got the houthis they've got uh
that just a lot of allies around the
area in syria and what um iran has done
they've got a lot of powerful military
they can do asymmetric warfare but
they have developed ballistic missiles
and a and and and these missiles are
very powerful a lot of them five to
seven hundred uh um kilogram um warheads
500 to 700 750 kilogram thousand
kilogram warheads these things that's a
devastating blast and they have them by
the many many thousands some believe
hundreds of thousands right tens of
thousands or hundreds of thousands of
these missiles
okay
and they can strike every base in the
middle east and they could fl so and if
you notice uh they struck a couple
american uh uh of bases they're very
accurate they can hit within a few feet
of their target um they fly fast they
fly low they're hard that you know some
of them are ground hugging so the bottom
line is look we couldn't stop those
ballistic missiles so if we could go to
a war with iran tomorrow
and if we did if they chose
um they could flatten every american
base in ours they could flatten the oil
fields of kuwait the oil fields of the
uae of bahrain of saudi arabia and what
would happen if that happened
the price of gas would be 25 50
a gallon i mean out it would destroy our
economy so fortu before for biden to
start a war with iran would be the end
of his presidency because when americans
felt the economic pain when they saw
that my god we've been thrown into a
depression that makes the um and i mean
the potential is there if the iranians
want to do it we could be thrown into a
depression the likes of which the united
states had never seen and i suspect joe
biden wouldn't come out too well when
the democrats in 2022 would be wiped out
wiped out if he started that we'd take a
beating in it would just completely
destabilize this country um because if
the iranians chose to maximum
retaliation my god and that's that
that's not uh i mean you got to add this
what would happen
in um
in europe what would happen all the
places around the world that depend on
middle eastern oil when all of a sudden
the iranians flatten the oil fields with
ballistic missiles and that potential is
there
so i while the neocons may want war with
uh
iran the reality of it is the um
the uh consequences the potential
consequences are far too high for any
politician who is not completely insane
to take i don't think joe biden takes
that i think he is doing everything he
can to hold israel off they're pushing
for it they want the u.s to do it
because israel knows their military is
not powerful enough to go toe-to-toe
with with uh iran they don't want to do
that
so they know they'd lose that when in a
conventional war
so um that's not an option
so right now i don't know where the
options are for the u.s military we know
the neocons are on biden the thing
that's is really
since i'm running out of time 28 i'll
finish up with this the thing that's
concerning is this
biden seems to be
making some kind of an argument or
there's been at least i've read it a lot
that he wants to pivot to asia so he
wants to get out of the middle east so
he can put all of these all the military
and and surround china and threaten
china well number one china's got a
powerful military and keep in mind
something
you're going to challenge china's
military on their own ground
and they have a lot of ballistic
missiles a lot of stuff they got a lot
of powerful stuff man we'd lose 40 50
000 soldiers the first day do you think
america is ready for that now let me add
this
china is the world's
uh industrial engine
if the united states went to war with
the world's industrial engine
right so tomorrow so right now um all of
our auto industry is waiting on um chips
from taiwan
because so there's 150 000 ford trucks i
mean everywhere they're waiting on ships
from taiwan right we go to war with
china stop waiting because they ain't
never coming
think about it walmart everything in
there is chinese out of business your
minimum dollar store out of business
most of the stores you go to out of
business not to mention there's a war
going on the clothes that come in from
the from asia from that are made in
vietnam bangladesh myanmar all of them
forget it all of them done there's a war
going on in that area so what would
happen if you're an american if we go to
war with china well let me add this
nike's out of business
all of the they're watching what you
think they're going to let you think
china if we go to war they're going to
let nike and microsoft and
and all these other companies keep
making stuff in their country that ain't
happening so all most of our major
companies all the stuff that amazon
sells probably 80 of it 90 of it's made
in china amazon what are they going to
sell now there's nothing no products
so
you go to the store tomorrow it's empty
go on amazon i'll buy something i'm
sorry all gone
it would that our number one trading
partner it would be gone overnight it
would be
the most
irresponsible move in the history of the
united states militarily to start a war
with china so the fact before you even
get to the part of nuclear of nuclear
exchange which ends all of humankind
even conventional
would be it wouldn't it would be going
to war with the united states it'd be
like i'm going to put a gun in my head
and threaten you hey
you you know you saw uh blazing saddles
hey if you don't cut that crap out i'm
gonna shoot myself right in the head
that's what starting a war with china
would be
russia do we really want to start that
russia's got as many nukes as we do what
are we gonna do attack them with nukes
number one number two
what are we going to do attack russia
and europe and their own ground we'd
lose that when their military is too
powerful it is a defensive military the
u.s ain't going to go up against russia
on their border there's a reason that
there's nato there's the u.s there's
france there's europe i mean there's
there's germany you know why all those
countries are stuck together because one
of them at a time can't
beat uh the us and right now nato does
not have the military resources to go
toe-to-toe with russia forget it it's
not happening
so that's not an option that again
that's suicide and so you've got let me
add this china doesn't want a war russia
doesn't want a war
so you're gonna have to actually fire on
them first to get the war started and
they'll they will fire back defensively
so the neocons are they got problems but
i suspect that um i'm suspecting they're
going to look at africa
that's what i think they're going to
look and we will see how things go from
there because god knows they're mad at
biden and their position is going to be
darn you joe biden you took our war and
and add this
and they and they're getting paid in
that war there's a lot of uh military
contractors that are upset now because
you know they they they um
you know they were eating off of
afghanistan and now they're like we need
a new country man we got to get paid and
where are we going to launder all this
money out of the national treasure
treasury enter our pockets from that's
the problem they got they want to eat
they want to eat well and without
another country to um uh uh to occupy it
it's harder to do that at any rate
thanks a lot um i will be back on
tomorrow uh i think john is not going to
be able to come on tomorrow you know the
holidays coming up i'm leaving friday so
you know i'll try to do another show
tomorrow but after that for the weekend
i'll be going until about monday or
tuesday floating around somewhere
at the beach and we'll go from there so
i'm trying to uh uh be online a lot
thanks everybody i will see you tomorrow
i'll try to do about eight o'clock
there's nikki king what's nikki have to
say putin said he has no desire to start
a war but he will now let an attack on
his country right well and that's any
country you know what i mean that's any
country countries if you attack
somebody's country they're gonna um
you know they're gonna respond let's
just hope that doesn't happen let's see
uh and i'm with sam clahan he says we
need a third party that's more focused
on america that's a fact because the two
more focused on america focused on
america at a period in any way shape or
form because the countries we have now
the company
the um
the parties that we have now
are they're getting paid and they're
crony billionaire corporate
uh supporters are getting paid and as
far as us they don't really care we're
looking at millions homes they could
care less they could care less we are um
fuel for the machine that's the way we
look all right i want to thank everybody
and um if you get a chance
make sure you share this on all of your
social media platforms i would
appreciate it if you're not watching
this on youtube if you could go to my
youtube channel if you could subscribe
if you could click the little um bell so
that you get notifications ideally and
um share from youtube that way more
people sign up i need we need to get
more people signed up tight lines
garland yeah yeah that's that sounds
like a fisherman to me i do a lot of
fishing i love it i was out on the boat
uh you know
all weekend will be again uh soon so
peace
thank you everybody for being a part of
this youtube channel and i am out